cms2cms.com 2019-10-04

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy applies to [CMS2CMS](https://cms2cms.com/) developed by MagneticOne.  
MagneticOne is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. We recognize the importance of protecting all the information provided by CMS2CMS service users, newsletter subscribers and all MagneticOne customers. All our customers and users are encouraged to read this privacy policy prior to submitting any personal information or using the website in any other manner.

## Information Collection and Usage

When signing up for CMS2CMS account, you are asked to provide with the following information:

  * name
  * e-mail address
  * password

When you visit CMS2CMS website, our server records the information sent from your browser:

  * web request (e.g. date, time, etc.)
  * IP address
  * browser type
  * browser language
  * one or more cookies identifying your browser

When migrating your CMS, you are asked to upload the bridge file to provide CMS2CMS access to your website. You may also be asked to provide your direct database connection to speed up the process. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner.

## We Keep Your Data Safe and Private

When it comes to protecting your private information, we’ve got it locked down tighter than Alcatraz. We partner with Amazon Web Services, use 128-bit SSL encryption, and create daily backups. And we never, EVER disclose any data to third-parties without your permission. Rest easy, nothing’s getting out of here alive.

## Information Security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.  
We restrict access to personal information to MagneticOne employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to disciplinary action, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

## Information Sharing

We do not share, sell or rent any kind of personal information provided by our users, customers or website visitors to third-parties. We ensure the confidentiality of your private data.  
Certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, which does not identify your personality, may be shared with third-parties to optimize CMS2CMS service. This may include the number of users that migrated to a particular CMS platform, the number of clicks on a certain ad, etc.

## Data Integrity

CMS2CMS processes personal information for the specific purposes it was collected for and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy statement. Data collection, storage and processing practices are constantly analyzed to ensure proper information adherence. All the procedures involving your website information are performed on highly secured servers. Only authorized staff has access to monitoring the migration process. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current. We count on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

## Enforcement

CMS2CMS ensures constant compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please address your questions or concerns about this privacy statement to contact[at]cms2cms[dot]com. As soon as any written complaint is received, CMS2CMS takes the responsibility to contact the complaining user with the necessary solutions. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between CMS2CMS and an individual.

## Communication

Through contact forms or similar submission available on the website, users can submit any type of information to CMS2CMS. It will never be made public or accessible to third-parties. Requests for service, support or additional information may be forwarded as needed to the appropriate departments in the company. This kind of notifications are retained for internal administrative purposes and are not disclosed to the outside sources.

## Notification of Changes

If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under which circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Users should check this policy frequently to keep abreast of any changes.  
Last updated: November 13, 2012
